come on clim abort Scholastics The Magic
School Bus for even more wild
rides now you can collect all the fun
and Scholastics The Magic School Bus
video collection cool with the frizz
Arnold Wanda and the rest of the
gang join them for all of their exciting
action-packed Adventures find out what
happens when Arnold swallows the bus in
the Magic School Bus for lunch check out
what's making ralie sick in the Magic
School Bus inside Ralphie wow when the
kids get trapped in a haunted house they
never know what the next sound is going
to be in the Magic School Bus in the
haunted house watch
this experience the wonderful world of
animal habitats in the Magic School Bus
hops
home make waves as the gang Journeys to
the ocean floor in the Magic School Bus
gets eaten this is so cool
Blast Off on a field trip that's out of
this world when the Magic School Bus
Gets Lost in Space come along class
collect all of Scholastics The Magic
School Bus videos so they can become
lasting additions to your video library
I'd say it's a perfect time for a f
[Music]
trip come on on the magics
de
seat belts everyone please let this be a
normal field trip with a [ __ ] no way
cruising on down Main Street you're
relaxed and feeling good next thing that
you know you
seeing octus in my neighborhood sling on
the sound wave swinging through the star
take a left do Tes pick your second
right P Mar on the magic scho Navigator
nostril I'm on the Magic School bu SP
PL magic scho drop the river of
lava Magic School such a fine thing to
do so stop your to the seat come on in
and don't be shy just to make your day
complete you might get baked into a p
mag step inside it's a wild
ride come on ride on the Magic School
Bus
[Music]
hey Rousy wait for
me W I can't move
[Music]
[Applause]
W yes how's it going
Liz aren't you psyched the Friz is
taking us to the beach today don't
forget we can't go until after our
reports then let's keep the reports
short da yep where there's a will
there's a way
we brought sand in a crab shell for our
two Beach things that go together report
didn't we Carlos wao a humongous wave at
10:00 see crabs dig in the sand so crabs
and sand go
together wi
out what did you bring
Ralphie ah hello everyone hi you
guys Phoebe phoei did you bring the tun
grass Ralphie have I ever let you down
did you bring the sun actually I
couldn't fit it in my napsack but I did
bring
this the sun in all its Glory at my old
school we weren't allowed to bring the
sun to
class how about you Tim check it out a
stunning portrait of the rock to go with
Wanda's muscle you did bring the muscle
didn't you Wanda
taada one muscle to go with Tim's Rock I
named him gusle the muscle Gus for short
who's Gus for short hi Kesha Gus is the
muscle I brought for the two Beach
things that go together at court
see oh no oh help oh bad oh bad bad oh
bad bad bad bad bad bad bad bad
something wrong I totally forgot about
the report you did you didn't bring
anything thing just my swimsuit in a
towel and a tuna fish sandwich uhoh
what's wrong with that I love tuna
sandwiches listen don't panic yet who's
your partner Arnold don't worry Arnold
likes reports he probably did the whole
thing himself where is Arnold
anyway Arnold hi guys
yuck what happened to your shoe I was
running and I sort of stepped into the
pond near our house and you were running
because you're in a hurry because you
couldn't wait to show me what you did
for our two Beach things to go together
report
right Mom I knew I forgot something you
mean you didn't bring anything
either just my bathing suit in a
towel and the scum on your shoe
scum and a tuna fish sandwich da what do
we think of that but do scum and a tuna
fish sandwich go together hey maybe they
do think think think think think think
think no oh great not only do I get
slimed by Pawn scum but I forget my
report I knew I should have stayed home
today
hey we can't just give up Arnold we have
to work with what we got but
kha oh good morning class good morning
Miss prle we have an exciting day ahead
of us haven't we hang T you guys maybe
she'll forget the reports and the first
thing on the agenda is your two Beach
things that go together reports then
again maybe she
won't let's start with um rfie and
Phoebe why the Sun and dun grass Go
Together by us all rights
reserved Doom grass like other plants
uses energy from the Sun to make its own
food no sun no Doom
grass no sun no
nothing oh Kesha and Arnold why don't
you go
next yes well
um we brought this um nutritious tuna
fish
sandwich and this delightful green scum
you did why that is absolutely
fantastic it
is so tell us what the connection is
between delightful green scum and a
nutritious tuna fish sandwich um uh um
they both have um
adjectives oh oh dear hold that thought
it's time to go to the beach oh but
don't worry we'll finish your reports
when we get back line up by the door
please Saved by the Bell yeah I never
thought I'd be glad to go on a field
trip
[Music]
oh for once a nice peaceful day at the
beach forget it Arnold everyone else
will have a wonderful time but we've got
work to do now concentrate how does your
scum go with my
sandwich you know class this trip just
might give you the answer you're looking
for I wonder if she knows we don't know
she knows everything well not exactly
everything it's your job as scientist to
look for connections connections you
mean how things go together exactly
[Music]
we're here everybody
out there's Doom grass with the sun
beaming down on
[Music]
it and here's a rock covered with Gus's
family look at them all it's a regular
Muscle
Beach car